{
  "listado": [
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "el chavo|del 8",
      "pregunta": "1",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "lionel|messi",
      "pregunta": "2",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "pennywise",
      "pregunta": "3",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "star|lord",
      "pregunta": "4",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "wall e",
      "pregunta": "5",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "albert|einstein",
      "pregunta": "6",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "marilyn|monroe",
      "pregunta": "7",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "angus|young",
      "pregunta": "8",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "vito|corleone",
      "pregunta": "9",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "tiger|woods",
      "pregunta": "10",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "john|wick",
      "pregunta": "11",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "carrie",
      "pregunta": "12",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "voldemort",
      "pregunta": "13",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "checo|perez",
      "pregunta": "14",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "freddie|mercury",
      "pregunta": "15",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "amy|winehouse",
      "pregunta": "16",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "muhammad|ali",
      "pregunta": "17",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "lebron|james",
      "pregunta": "18",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "daniel|larusso",
      "pregunta": "19",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Merlina",
      "pregunta": "20",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "shaggy",
      "pregunta": "21",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "spike lee",
      "pregunta": "22",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "meteoro",
      "pregunta": "23",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "harry|potter",
      "pregunta": "24",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "el guason",
      "pregunta": "25",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "walter|white",
      "pregunta": "26",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "michael|jordan",
      "pregunta": "27",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "elvis|presley",
      "pregunta": "28",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "miguel",
      "pregunta": "29",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "ed|sheeran",
      "pregunta": "30",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "indiana|jones",
      "pregunta": "31",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "slash",
      "pregunta": "32",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "ant man",
      "pregunta": "33",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "frankenstein",
      "pregunta": "34",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "hannibal|lecter",
      "pregunta": "35",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "stan|lee",
      "pregunta": "36",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "alfred|hitchcock",
      "pregunta": "37",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "shang chi",
      "pregunta": "38",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Ellen|DeGeneres",
      "pregunta": "39",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "demogorgon",
      "pregunta": "40",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "alex|morgan",
      "pregunta": "41",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "chester",
      "pregunta": "42",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "diego|maradona",
      "pregunta": "43",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "once",
      "pregunta": "44",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "dr strange",
      "pregunta": "45",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "boba fett",
      "pregunta": "46",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "sheldon|cooper",
      "pregunta": "47",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "la mujer|maravilla",
      "pregunta": "48",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "john|lennon",
      "pregunta": "49",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "hermione|granger",
      "pregunta": "50",
      "categoria": "Funkos"
    }
  ]
}
